I'm scared.
(悟)＜怖い｡
自分の心に踏み込むのが 怖い＞
I'm scared to get
to the heart of my own mind.
(編集者)うーん｡➡
I think you're doing good work here.
そつなく描けているとは
思うんだけどね｡➡
But how can I say this...
でも 何というか➡
BOYS' FLIGHT
もっと踏み込んで描かないと➡
If you don't dig deeper,
the readers won't be
able to see you in the work.
作品から見えてこないんですよ➡
あなたの顔が｡➡
You're 29, right?
29歳でしたよね？➡
That's kind of a tough fit
for our magazine.
ああ…
うちでは ちょっと難しいな｡
26 more days until the 2006 World Cup
begins in Germany...
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ](女性)2006年 ワールドカップ
ドイツ大会開幕まで あと…｡
Every day, the words cross my mind.
"If I had done this back then..."
＜日々 心によぎる あのとき
こうしていればという言葉＞
But they don't take
the sincere form of regret.
＜でも それは 後悔という
切実な形を取ることもなく➡
The words are just an excuse
that come to mind, then disappear.
浮かんでは消えていく
言い訳の言葉だ＞
＜俺は
自分の心に踏み込むのが 怖い＞
I'm scared to get
to the heart of my own mind.
ERASED
I'm going out on a delivery.
(悟)配達 出ます｡
(高橋)おお 気を付けてな｡
Okay. Be careful.
I'm going out on a delivery, too.
(愛梨)
片桐も 配達 行ってきまーす｡
Okay, be careful!
(高橋)はい！ 気を付けて！
(愛梨)あっ 藤沼さん
ピザ 途中で食べちゃ駄目だよ｡
Fujinuma, don't eat any pizza on the way.
《拾えねえ｡
平成生まれのジョークか》
I don't get it.
What is that, a Gen Y joke?
Wasn't planning to.
食わねえよ｡
That girl says the same thing
to me every time I see her.
《あの子 顔 合わすたびに
同じ せりふ言うな》
In fact, it's the only thing she's said to me.
《つうか
それ以外 話したことない》
It doesn't seem like
she has any special feelings for me.
《俺に 特別な感情があるようにも
見えない》
Weird girl...
《変な女》
Well, not like I'm interested
in high school girls...
《まあ 俺も がきには…》
I'm positive.
《間違いない… また あれだ》
It happened again.
Where is it?
《どこだ？
どこかに違和感が…》
What seems out of place?
Hey, trucker! Stop!
おい！ そこのトラック 止まれ！
おい！ 運転手！
Hey! Driver!
(クラクション)
F-Fujinuma?
ふ… 藤沼さん？
何やって…｡
What are you...
Dammit!
チクショー…｡
I shouldn't have gotten involved!
《やっぱ 関わるんじゃなかった》
《だけど…》
But...
- Are you okay?!
- That was close!
(女性)大丈夫？
(男性)危なかったな｡
≪(クラクション)
What the hell is this?
《何だ？ これ》
《ああ… 走馬灯ってやつだ》
That thing where my life
flashes before my eyes...
There, see?
《ほらな やっぱ 他人と関わると
ろくなことがねえ》
Nothing good comes of getting
involved with strangers.
Oh well...
《まあ いいか…》
My dying doesn't make any difference.
《この世から
俺が いなくなったところで…》
Huh?
《あれ？》
His eyes opened.
《目が 開いた》
Good morning, Fujinuma!
(愛梨)おはよう 藤沼さん｡
２日 たったよ｡
You were out for two days!
うっ…｡
ああ…｡
Katagiri?
片桐君？
Do you know who you are
and why you're here?
自分が 誰かとか
今 ここにいる理由とか分かる？
Satoru Fujinuma, 29 years old.
藤沼 悟 29歳…｡
I was chasing a truck
and got into an accident.
トラックを追い掛けて 事故った｡
Good! The doctor said
you hardly suffered any injuries.
よかった！
外傷は ほとんどないって｡
It's a miracle!
奇跡だね｡
Do you want me to call someone?
誰かに 連絡 取ってあげようか？
友達とか 彼女さんとかさ｡
A friend or girlfriend?
Nah. There's nobody
I want to bother telling.
いいよ｡ わざわざ
知らせたいやつは いない｡
Snip-snip.
チョキチョキ｡
What's that?
何だよ？ それ｡
平成生まれのジョーク？
A Gen Y joke?
It's like you're covered
with a thin membrane.
何か 薄い膜で
覆われてるみたいだから｡
You don't seem like the type
who opens up to people.
藤沼さんって
他人に 心 開かなそうだもんね｡
笑わないしさ｡
でも ちょっと見直したよ｡
You never laugh either.
But I do kind of see you in a new light.
How's that?
何が？
子供 助けたでしょ？
You saved a kid's life, right?
I was there.
私 あの現場にいたんだよ｡
They say the truck driver died
of a heart attack while driving.
トラックの運転手 心臓発作で
運転中に死んでたんだって｡
I'm surprised you noticed it.
よく気付いたなぁって｡
I just got lucky.
たまたまだよ｡
After that, the truck
crashed into a warehouse,
トラック あの後
倉庫に突っ込んで➡
so you and the driver
were the only casualties.
死傷者は
運転手と藤沼さんだけだったよ｡
Casualties...
《死傷者…》
After I explained everything
to the manager,
店長には ちゃんと話したから｡
he said, "Tell him not to worry about the bike
or the car he hit, just come back to work."
バイクも 当てた車のことも
気にせず 戻ってこいって｡
Thanks.
ありがとう｡
あっ ちょっと笑った｡
You smiled for a second there!
片桐君はさ
何で バイトしてんの？
Katagiri, why do you work there?
へえー｡
意外と 踏み込んでくるんだ｡
I'm surprised you got
right to the heart of it.
Did I?
あっ… そうかな？
Yeah. No one's ever
asked me that before.
うん｡
その質問されたのって 初めてだよ｡
I have a dream.
私 夢があるんだ｡
I see.
そっか｡
That's all you're gonna ask me?!
そこまでしか聞かないの!?
Hey...
なあ
人に 夢とか話しちまってさ➡
When you tell other people
about your dream...
don't you think, like,
"But what if it doesn't happen for me?"
実現しなかったら どうしようとか
思わない？
I'm not especially
embarrassed to talk about it.
別に 恥ずかしいとか思わない｡
I feel like if you say
the words over and over,
言葉ってさ
口に出して言ってるうちに➡
it'll actually happen
somewhere along the line.
ホントになる気がする｡
Those words...
《その言葉
何だか とても懐かしい感じだ》
For some reason, they resonate with me.
But I'm not going to tell you
what it is, Fujinuma.
でも まっ
藤沼さんには教えないんだけどね｡
It's not like we're close or anything.
えっ？
別に そんな親しいわけじゃないし｡
Well, I'll tell the nurse you're awake,
then I'm going home.
じゃあ 看護師さん呼んだら
直帰するね｡
Bye-bye.
バイバイ｡
≪(戸の閉まる音)
Weird girl...
《変な女》
I call the phenomenon "Revival."
＜あの現象を
俺は リバイバルと呼んでいる＞
Even though I know it's not beneficial
for me, I always get involved.
＜損することは 分かってるのに
関わってしまう＞
I usually go back
between one and five minutes,
＜だいたい
１分から５分くらい前に戻って➡
where everything is the same as before.
同じ光景を見る＞
It's always right before
something bad happens.
＜決まって
何か 悪いことが起こる直前だ＞
I find myself searching for the thing
that doesn't feel right,
＜まるで 誰かに お前が防げと
強制されてるかのように➡
as if someone put me there
with the order to "Prevent it!"
違和感を探している自分がいる＞
As a result, I've kept trouble
from happening again and again.
＜結果 何度となく
トラブルを回避してきた＞
In most cases, negative
incidents just come out even.
＜その ほとんどが➡
ﾏｲﾅｽだったことが
ﾌﾟﾗﾏｲｾﾞﾛになるだけのことで…＞
Once in a while, it turns negative for me.
＜たまに 今回みたく 自分にとって
マイナスになったりする＞
Welcome home, Satoru.
(佐知子)ああ おかえり 悟｡
母さん…｡
Mom...
I went to the hospital,
but you were still sleeping,
病院 行ったんだけどさ
あんた 寝てるし➡
which was boring so I came here.
つまんないから
こっち 来ちゃった｡
Is your head all right?
頭は 大丈夫なのかい？
大丈夫｡
Fine.
I was shocked.
びっくりしたべさ｡
正面衝突って 聞いたからさ｡
I mean, they said
it was a head-on collision.
I'm going to stay with you for a while.
当分 ここに住むから｡
えっ!? 何だよ それ｡
Why would you do that?
My adorable son's head
hit a moving vehicle.
カワイイ 一人息子が
頭 打ったんだ｡
The least I can do is watch over him.
様子見くらい いいっしょ｡
I said I'm fine.
だから 大丈夫だって｡
布団だって 一組しかねえし｡
And I only have one futon.
There's a sleeping bag in the closet.
That works for me.
押し入れに寝袋あったから
私 それでいいよ｡
えっ…｡ ホテル 行けよ｡
お金 もったいないっしょ｡
Go to a hotel.
It's a waste of money.
Oh, that's right! I'll reimburse you
for the hospital charges!
あっ そうだ｡ 入院費 返すよ｡
じゃ それが 宿代ってことで｡
Keep it. We'll use it
to pay for my room here.
I'm her son,
《実の息子の俺でさえ➡
but even I can't believe she's 52 years old,
because the woman never changes.
52歳とは思えないほど
昔のまんまだ》
Satoru, can you get to Ueno
without changing trains?
悟 上野って
電車一本で行ける？
No. Figures. You're here
for sightseeing, aren't you?
行けねえ｡
やっぱ 観光かよ｡
I have come all the way from Hokkaido.
せっかく
北海道から出てきたんだし➡
Besides, I'd get bored having to
look at your face every day.
毎日 あんたの顔 見てても
つまんないっしょ｡
You haven't even seen me
for a full day yet.
《まだ 丸一日も
見てねえじゃんかよ》
Come on, let's eat.
さあ 食べるべ｡
Sorry. I took your futon and TV.
(佐知子)悪いね
布団と テレビ もらっちゃって｡
Yeah, don't worry about it.
ああ いいよ｡
I'd rather have that
than try to be quiet if I go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night.
《そんなことより
夜中 トイレに行くとき➡
気を使う方が 嫌なんだ》
Look, you don't have to tiptoe around me
if you use the toilet in the middle of the night.
あのさ 夜中 トイレ行くときとか
気 使わなくていいから｡
I won't wake up.
私 起きないからさ｡
《妖怪め》
Yokai...
On to our next story.
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ](男性)
さて 次のニュースです｡➡
The first-grade girl from Saitama
who went missing yesterday evening
昨日 ８日の夕方から
行方不明になっていた➡
さいたま市内の
小学１年生 女児が➡
was found safe and sound
this morning on a road in Yokohama.
今日 午前 横浜市内の路上で
無事 保護されました｡
Hey, Satoru...
She was taken to the hospital
but suffered no injuries.
悟さ 覚えてる？
何？
Do you remember?
What?
What happened in the neighborhood
when you were in fifth grade.
あんたが 小学校５年のとき
近所で起きた事件｡
The Ina Police Station has reported
that an unemployed man
Your memories are probably hazy.
記憶 薄いでしょ｡
from Nishi-ku, Yokohama
was with the girl at the scene.
We tried desperately then
He has been arrested on suspicion
of abducting a minor.
私たち 必死だったのさ｡
to get you kids to forget
even a little of what happened.
あんたたちから 事件の記憶を
少しでも 取り除こうとしたんだ｡
Your life was in danger.
あんた 危ないとこだったんだよ｡
When I was in fifth grade...
《俺が 小５のとき 誘拐事件…》
An abduction...
Two of my classmates went missing.
《クラスメートが
２人 いなくなったんだった》
Go! Go, go!
≪(足音)
When I was little, a local guy,
Yuuki, often played with me.
＜幼いころ ユウキさんという
二十歳くらいのお兄さんが➡
よく遊んでくれていた＞
His name really wasn't Yuuki,
but that's what I called him
＜ユウキは 名前じゃなく➡
｢勇気｣ ｢勇気｣を連発するから
そう呼んでいた＞
because he'd always say,
"Yuuki, yuuki! Courage, courage..."
W-Want me to guess about the most
p-popular kid in your class?
(白鳥)《き… 君のクラスの
人気者のこと 当ててみようか？》
(悟)《えっ？》
(白鳥)《そいつはさ➡
He's cheerful and good at sports.
明るくて スポーツが得意》
He speaks his mind
and sometimes screws around,
《はっきり 物を言って
ふざけることもあるけど➡
but is serious
when it comes to one thing.
何か 一つの物事に対して
真面目なやつ》
(悟)《すげえ…》
That's incredible.
Popular people are usually that guy.
《人気者って
だいたい そんなやつだよ》
W-What if you tried imitating him?
《ま… まねしてみたら
どうかな？ 一つでも二つでも》
In one or two areas.
Just as much as you can, without being
embarrassed, but with courage.
《できることだけ
恥ずかしがらず 勇気を持って》
Six months after the disappearances,
Jun Shiratori was arrested
＜事件から半年後➡
連続誘拐殺人犯として
捕まったのは 白鳥 潤＞
as a serial kidnapper and murderer.
It was Yuuki.
＜ユウキさんだった＞
Episode 1
Flashing Before My Eyes
You bought way too much.
いくら何でも 買い過ぎじゃねえ？
(佐知子)重過ぎたかい？➡
Is it too heavy for you?
Well, you can have curry for days.
まっ カレーは
何日でも食べられるっしょ｡
≪(男の子)うっ…｡
Ah, see?
(泣き声)
(男の子の母)あらら｡
This is why I told you not to run.
だから 走るなって言ったのに｡
もう一個 買いに戻ろうか｡
Let's go back and get you another one.
(店員)あっ！
Satoru, what's wrong?
うん？ 悟 なした？
うん？ いや…｡
Nothing...
Is it too heavy for you?
(佐知子)重過ぎたかい？➡
Well, you can have curry for days.
まっ カレーは
何日でも食べられるっしょ｡
Revival?
《リバイバルかよ…》
≪(男の子)うっ…｡
Ah, see?
あらら｡
This is why I told you not to run.
だから 走るなって言ったのに｡
もう一個 買いに戻ろうか｡
Let's go back and get you another one.
Crap. I don't know what it is!
《まずい｡ 分からない…｡
何だ？ 何が起きる？》
Come on...
What's gonna happen?
Mom... Would you look around?
母さん 周りを見てくれないか？
えっ？
Don't you... have a weird feeling?
何かさ
ちょっと 変な感じがしないか？
What are you talking about?
何 言ってんの？ あんた｡➡
Come to think of it, you once told me
the same thing a long time ago.
そういや あんた 昔も
同じこと言ったときがあったね｡
Did I?
そうだっけ？
(佐知子)あんときは ぼや騒ぎ｡
It was about a small fire back then.
(店員)あっ！
(佐知子)うん？
Was he... looking at me?
(佐知子)《私を… 見てた？》
Nothing happened?
《何も起きなかったのか？》
[TEL](シャッター音)
Fujinuma!
≪(愛梨)藤沼さ～ん！➡
Hey!
お～い！
SCHOOL ROUTE
I don't believe it! Your mother?!
(愛梨)えっ 嘘!? お母さん!?
絶対 お姉さんだと思ったよ｡
I thought she was your big sister!
Do you believe in yokai?
妖怪って信じるか？
(愛梨)今日から 信じるよ｡➡
I do from today.
But are you fighting?
てか ケンカしてんの？
いや…｡
No.
Your name is Airi?
あっ…｡ 愛梨さん… だっけ？
カレー作るけど 食べていかない？
I'm making curry for dinner.
Would you like to eat over?
I am Airi Katagiri!
片桐 愛梨です！ いただきます！
お手伝いします！
Thanks for the invite!
I'll help you make it, too!
She's coming over?
《食うのか…》
I'm starving!
(愛梨)もう おなか ぺこぺこです｡
You drew manga?!
(愛梨)
えっ!? 漫画 描いてたんだ！
You're surprised?
意外だったか？
No, not at all.
(愛梨)ううん 全然｡ ホントだ｡
ウィキタニカに載ってる｡
It's true. You've got
your own Wikitanika entry.
Don't do a search on me.
調べんなよ｡
(愛梨)何で？ すごいじゃん！
Why not? It's great!
Well, let's eat.
(佐知子)さあ 食べよう｡
It's not great. That's why
I don't want you to do it.
《すごくねえから 嫌なんだ》
Thank you for the meal!
(愛梨)いただきまーす！
う～ん！ おいしい！
(佐知子)ありがとう｡
It's delicious!
Thank you.
At first I thought you were too young
to be his girlfriend, but you're not his girlfriend.
彼女にしちゃ 若過ぎると思ったけど
違うんだ｡ 料理も上手なのにな｡
Too bad, you're a good cook.
Sorry we're not dating.
ごめんなさい｡ 違います｡
To me, Fujinuma is, how can I put it?
藤沼さんは 何ていうか
尊敬できる お友達です｡
A friend I can respect.
What? Is it too spicy?
何？ 辛過ぎたかい？
いや… うめえよ｡
No, it's good.
Thank you again!
(愛梨)ごちそうさまでした！
Well, I'll give you a lift to the station.
じゃあ 駅まで送ってくよ｡
You're going home already?
(佐知子)えっ もう帰るの？➡
You should spend the night.
泊まっていけばいいのに｡
片桐君は 高校生だぞ｡
Katagiri is a high school student.
Thanks for having me over
for dinner, Satoru.
(愛梨)ごちそうになった上に
ありがとう 悟さん｡
No problem.
いいさ｡
警官だけ 見張っててくれよ｡
Just keep an eye out for cops.
Sure.
うん｡
≪(ドアの閉まる音)
Welcome home.
おかえり｡
She's my co-worker.
バイトの後輩だぞ｡
Don't look at her
as potential wife material.
嫁探ししてるみたいな
浅ましい目で見るなよ｡
You're dense.
あんたも鈍いね｡
あの子は 脈ありだべさ｡
You have a chance with that girl.
She said she respects you.
尊敬してるってさ｡
だから そんなんじゃねえし！
I'm telling you, it's not like that!
She was just being polite.
Don't take it seriously!
社交辞令 真に受けんなよ！
That Airi girl isn't the diplomatic type.
あの子… 愛梨ちゃんは
社交辞令なんて言わないべ｡
うん？
そうそう➡
Oh, by the way, the landlady
came over for the rent.
さっき 大家さんが
家賃 取りに来たよ｡
Is that right?
ああ そう｡
悟… 昼間の件だけど…｡
Satoru... About this afternoon...
In the supermarket parking lot...
えっ？
スーパーの駐車場の｡
ああ…｡ それが どうした？
What about it?
The abduction case was never solved.
誘拐事件が 未遂に終わったよ｡
えっ 何だって!?
What?!
I'm obviously kidding.
冗談に決まってるべさ｡
The Hokkaido Elementary School Student Serial Killer Case
The Last Serial Killer
of the Showa Era
Death-row Inmate Jun Shiratori
NIPPON
SHOWA'S MOST SHOCKING CRIMES
KAYO HINAZUKI (10 YEARS OLD)
うん？
I remember.
《思い出した》
That girl was one of my classmates,
one who was abducted 18 years ago.
《あの子は 18年前の誘拐事件で
いなくなったクラスメートの一人》
Kayo Hinazuki.
《雛月 加代》
She was always at the park alone.
《いつも 一人で公園にいた｡
友達ってわけじゃなかったけど…》
It's not like we were friends, but...
That was the last time I saw Hinazuki.
《あれが
雛月を見た 最後の姿だった》
I could've saved her!
《僕なら
助けられたはずなのに！》
If I'd said, "Let's walk home together,"
Hinazuki would still be...
《僕が あのとき 一緒に
帰ろうって言えば 雛月は…》
That's the thought
I wanted to forget the most.
《それこそが
自分が 一番 忘れたかった思い》
And Mom probably really did
try to erase it from my memory.
《そして おそらく➡
母が 俺から
本当に消そうとしていたもの》
If you don't dig deeper,
《もっと踏み込んで描かないと➡
the readers won't be
able to see you in the work.
作品から見えてこないんですよ
あなたの顔が》
"Wa" on the plate means it's a rental.
(佐知子)
《｢わ｣ナンバーは レンタカー》➡
That was definitely
an attempted abduction.
《あれは 間違いなく 誘拐だ》➡
Did he change his mind
because he saw me?
《私を見て
連れ去るのをやめた？》➡
He hid his face when our eyes met.
《あの反応は
顔を隠した… だべ》➡
He knew me.
《あいつは 私を知ってた》➡
And I know him from someplace.
《あの目の男を 私は知ってる》➡
It's on the tip of my tongue...
《喉まで 出かかってるのに…｡
どこで？ いつ？》
Where? When?
(佐知子)あっ｡
Serial Abductions and Murder
One Culprit Responsible for Kidnappings
I remember!
(佐知子)《思い出した…
あの目の男が 誰かを》
That man, he...
The killer...
《犯人…
ホントに 白鳥君じゃないのかも》
It may not have been Shiratori after all!
Hello?
(佐知子)もしもし｡
久しぶり｡ 藤沼 佐知子です｡
Long time no talk.
It's Sachiko Fujinuma.
18 years ago, so the statute
of limitations is up...
(佐知子)
《18年前の事件は 時効》➡
But...
《だけど 同じような手口で➡
I'm positive he committed the same crime
with the same basic M.O. over and over.
何度も 犯行を繰り返しているに
違いない》
That case isn't closed yet.
《あの事件は
まだ 終わっていない》
I have to talk to Satoru.
《悟と話さなくちゃ…》
The time has finally come
to talk to him about it.
《とうとう あのときのことを
話すときが来たんだ》
≪(ドアの開く音)
Satoru?
≪(足音)
(佐知子)悟…｡
♬～
I was right...
(佐知子)《やっぱり…》➡
Have to... call Satoru...
《悟に 電話しなくちゃ
帰ってくるなって…》➡
Tell him not to come home...
and I have to apologize.
《そして 謝らなくっちゃ…》
I could've saved her!
《僕なら
助けられたはずなのに！》
I'm sure it wasn't Yuuki!
《絶対 絶対
ユウキさんじゃない！》
It wasn't Yuuki, Mom!
《ユウキさんじゃないんだよ！
お母さん！》
I should have believed him then.
(佐知子)《あのとき
信じてあげるべきだった…》➡
Even if the police didn't...
《警察が信じなくても➡
I should've believed him.
私が
信じてあげなきゃいけなかった》
Satoru...
(佐知子)《悟…》➡
I'm sorry...
《ごめんね…》
Well, I'm off! See you tomorrow!
じゃあ 上がりまーす！
お疲れさまです！
Yeah, see you tomorrow!
おう お疲れ！
(愛梨)お疲れさま！
- See you tomorrow!
- See you!
Oh yeah, Satoru...
そうだ 悟さん｡
うん？
How about I guess what you had
for breakfast this morning?
朝ご飯 何 食べたか当てようか？
はっ？
Curry!
カレー｡
当たり｡
You're right.
Yes!
よっしゃ！
《そりゃ あの量 あれば➡
With as much as she made, of course
I'm gonna eat it for breakfast too.
朝も食うだろ》
Hey, ask your mom
if I can put in a request.
(愛梨)ねえ また お母さんに
リクエストしていいか 聞いて｡
That curry was so good!
すっごく おいしかったよ
あのカレー！
All right, all right.
分かった 分かった｡
じゃあな｡
See you.
(愛梨)うん？
♬～
Sheesh...
ったく…｡ うん？
Gimme a break...
しゃあねえな｡
Mom! What are you doing?
母さん 何やってんだ｡
北海道の実家じゃねえんだぞ｡
This isn't your house back in Hokkaido.
At least lock the door.
鍵くらい しめろよ｡
Hey...
おい…｡ おい…｡
返事しろよ｡
Hey...
Answer me.
No way... Cut it out.
嘘だろ？ やめろって…｡
Wake up! Mom!
起きろよ｡ 母さん｡
うわー！
Mr. Fujinuma, last night
your mother shared curry with me...
(大家)藤沼さん 昨日 お母さんに
お裾分けしてもらった…｡
(悲鳴)
Wait!
ちょっと待って…｡
CHIBA PREFECTURAL POLICE
Mr. Fujinuma had blood on his hands...
(大家)
藤沼さんの手が 血まみれで…｡
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
藤沼 悟さんですか？
I need to take you down to the station...
What is this?
《何だ？ これ》
Wrong. You're wrong.
《違う… 違う｡
俺じゃ… 俺じゃ》
It wasn't me...
It wasn't me!
Hey, don't run!
ちょっと 君！
Did I...
《リバイバル… したのか？》
have another Revival?
But where am I?
《けど ここは…》
I know I've seen it before...
《見覚えあるけど 何か…》
but somehow...
≪(足音)
Yo, Satoru! You're gonna be late!
よう 悟！
遅刻するぞ！
Huh? Who's that again?
《あれ？ 誰だっけ？
ランドセル？》
A backpack?
♬～
Ice Hockey Club 1988 National Champions
1988?
昭和63年？
♬～